I specifically on the Dark Factory,
which I believe is what I'm here to talk about today.
I don't think we can do this.
Got Anthropic
coming out and saying, hey, we rewrote Bun from Zig to Rust in two weeks.
And we realized we're not being ambitious by quite a long way.
The concept of a dark factory is for manufacturing,
but the lights are not on because there are no humans inside.
To me, this is the new software engineering.
This is what it looks like.
I think there was a very clear moment
where we just decided the only way out is through.
We intentionally ran really fast and straight into many walls.
She basically had built this orchestrator on, say, what, like a Thursday,
then told it to improve itself over the weekend.
Like, we are shipping faster. I think every week or two
we go about 30% faster than we did the week before.
And it doesn't seem to be tapering off yet.
I mean, we're happy to be the guinea pigs.
We'll see if it works.